Aleksandr Yanyuk

Greater Sacramento



alex745i@gmail.com



9165791657



linkedin.com/in/aleksandr-yanyuk-17b09b257

Summary

I enjoy breaking difficult problems into small tasks to bring clarity to everyday tools. I enjoy being an active team member who uses clear communication and collaboration day to day. I have experience in the following:

Main Languages: C#, JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5, TypeScript, SCSS

Databases: Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL, T-SQL, Azure Studio SQL, LINQ, Entity Framework Core

Frameworks: .NET Core, ASP.NET Core MVC, ASP.NET Web APIs, Bootstrap, Angular 13, NgRx, Redux, Jasmine & Karma, Selenium WebDriver, Kendo UI, jQuery

Other: GitHub, JIRA, HTTPS, TCP/IP, Agile/Scrum, AWS, Azure, AWS Lambda, RESTful API, Redux Dev Tools, Postman, Enterprise Code Development, CI/CD: Jenkins, AWSCodeBuild, Microsoft Azure App Services

Experience



Software Engineer

Prosper IT Consulting

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023 (4 months)

- Worked on a local movie theatre called Theatre Vertigo, which was built using ASP.NET MVC C#
- •Attended daily agile/scrum stand ups and used Microsoft Azure DevOps for collaboration.
- •Used Git for version control and reviewed peers pull request.
- Created Model using C# for calendar event CRUD Functionality.
- •Used Entity Framework to create a new table in Microsoft SQL Server using the above model.
- •Added a controller for Create, Delete, Edit and Index for the event calendar.
- •Created a contact page and added bootstrap and CSS for styling.

Software Engineer

Software Engineer Freelance

Feb 2022 - Nov 2022 (10 months)

Education



THE TECH Academy

Software Engineer/Full Stack Developer

2022 - 2023

- Completed the Software Developer Bootcamp with over 800 hours of hands on experience.
- Trained to program/develop in several computing languages such as C#, ASP.NET MVC, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL which are necessary for Full-Stack Development.

- · Learned and developed using technologies/frameworks such as, to .NET Framework, Microsoft's Entity Framework, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, jQuery, CSS Bootstrap, Back-End and Front-End web development.
- · Learned about and Agile Scrum methodology, Object-Oriented Principles and used version control Git.

Licenses & Certifications



C# .NET - The Tech Academy

Skills

Back-End Web Development • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • ASP.NET Web API • Language Integrated Query (LINQ) • Application Support • Full-Stack Development • Agile Software Development • SQL Database • Web Applications • Model-View-Controller (MVC)